Guide to the Stanford Macintosh Users' Group Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Macintosh Users' Group records
1984-1990
SC0378
Stanford Macintosh Users' Group.
2 Linear feet
Correspondence, memorabilia, financial records, newsletters, telephone memo books, and other miscellaneous records pertaining to their activities on campus.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of James H. Lewinson, 1990.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Stanford Macintosh Users' Group is a volunteer organization composed of Stanford University students and community members whose purpose is to act as a clearinghouse to exchange information about the Apple Macintosh computer.
Description of the Collection
Correspondence, memorabilia, financial records, newsletters, telephone memo books, and other miscellaneous records pertaining to their activities on campus.
Access Terms
Apple Computer, Inc.; Stanford Macintosh Users' Group.; Macintosh (Computer)
Collection Contents
- General Records, Series 1
  - Accounts Payable, 5/1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounts Payable, 6/1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accounts Payable, 7/1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Accounts Payable, 8/1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accounts Payable, 9/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Accounts Payable, 10/1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Accounts Payable, 11/1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Accounts Payable, 12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Accounts Payable, 1/1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Accounts Payable, 2/1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Accounts Payable, 3/1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Accounts Payable, 4/1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Accounts Payable, 5/1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Accounts Payable, 6/1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Accounts Payable, 7/1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Accounts Payable, 8/1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Accounts Payable, 9/1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Accounts Payable, 10/1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Accounts Payable, 11/1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Accounts Payable, 12/1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Accounting Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 5/1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 6/1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 7/1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 8/1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 9/1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 10/1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 11/1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1/1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Feb (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Apr (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 May (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Jun (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Jul (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Aug (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Sep (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Oct (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Nov (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - ASSU Account #7651, 1988 Dec (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 5/1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 6/1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 7/1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 8/1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 9/1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 10/1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 11/1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 12/1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 1/1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 2/1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 3/1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 4/1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 5/1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 6/1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 7/1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 8/1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 9/1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 10/1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 11/1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ASSU Account #7652, 12/1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - canceled ChecksI Mise. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence Received, 10/1985-1/1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Facility Usage Request Forms, 11/21/1984-6/11/1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Forms--Sample Layouts, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - General Meeting Manpower" Forms, 8/5/1985-ca.10/1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Interdeparbnental Requests (for Technicians at Meetings), 11/26/1984-2/24/1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - MaCWorld Expo Info: 1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mail Manager--Correspondence, Order Forms, 9/1986-3/1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Money Receipts, 11/26/1984-3/4/1985; 9/19/1988-7/10/1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter start-up Info. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Newsletters, 3/1985-12/1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, 1/1990-4/1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Organizational Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Student Organizational services (80s) Documentation, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - SOS Papers: 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Telecammunications Info: 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Work Information Center Requests: 11/1/1984-2/24/1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Telephone Records, Series 2
  - Telephone Memo Book, 3/10/1986-9/12/1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Memo Book, 9/15/1986-ca. 3/18/1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Telephone Memo Book, 7/8/1987-4/12/1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)